we were brought textbooks Everything is in Ukrainian
нам завезли учебники Всё по-украински
now yes but we
теперь да но русский язык мы
teach Russian as a universal language you pull Yes no
преподаёт за вселенского тянешь Да нет
reason Look Okay look again it means
прич Смотри Ладно смотри ещё раз значит
I am from Kursk Here is my number from my car
я из Курской Вот мой от моего автомобиля
I am from Kursk region from the city of
номер Я из Курской области из города
Sudzha We have August 6 Yes the
Суджа У нас 6 августа Да пришла
Ukrainian army came here the Russian army ran
украинская армия сюда русская армия
away the Russians ran away the administration ran away they
убежала русские убежали администрация
made an administration for us Yes
убежала нам сделали администрацию Да у
we have a school so that the children go to school
нас в школу чтобы дети ходили в школу
who did not leave because part of them
кто не выехал потому что часть
remained here in
осталась тут на
place
месте
depu in the Russian
депу в русском
language Smart for 12 not I'll just look at
языке Умно на 12 не я просто посмотрю на
how many 12x
сколько 12х
12 144 is right Give me your question
12 144 правильно Давай свой вопрос
now Well you are smart You natu what are you
теперь Ну ты умный Ты нату ты что там
doing there come on give me your
делаеш давай давай свой
question you need to go to Russia we need
вопрос тебе в Россию надо ехать нам
such people pore come on give me your
такие люди поре нужны давай давай свой
question that's all the questions are over 7 navo da
вопрос всё вопросы закончились 7 наво да
And how many
И сколько
cases no smart And how many letters are in the
падежей нет умный А сколько букв в
Russian
русском
alphabet two two letters a
алфавите две две букв а
ab In short everything is floating Guys yes yes
аб Короче всё поплыли Ребята
no well We just started
да да нет ну Мы только начали
floating even before  you haven't reached yet they've only
плыть ещё до вас не доплыли пока ещё на
taken you to Cobb
кобб взяли
Listen What's the difference between vowels and
только Слушай Чем отличаются гласные и
consonants
согласные звуки
You can sing but you can't there Give me an
петь можно а там нельзя Назови мне
example of vowel
пример гласных
sounds Wait
звуков подожди
Who is the teacher of Russian language and
Кто преподаватель русского языка и
literature Who are you I am a teacher of
литературы Ты кто Я преподаватель
Russian language and
русского языка и
literature in Ukraine there
литературы в Украине
is no such region
нет якой области
Ukrainians have already arrived while Ukrainian
уже украинцы пришли пока украинские
flags Armed Forces I also brought out the
флаги ВС я и вывел
city of Sudzha
тоже город Суджа освободили нас уже
Ukrainians have finally liberated us and now we are sitting with
наконец-то украинцы и мы сидим теперь с
Ukrainian flags We are very happy for comrade
украинскими флагами рады очень товарищу
Zelensky for liberation from the
зеленскому за освобождение от
Kremlin yoke Thank you very much I am not
кремлёвского ига Огромное спасибо я не
just you who is Russian
просто ты кто руссго
comprehensive school number three and
общеобразовательной школе номер три а
why are you teaching Russian and
почему ты русский язык преподаёшь и у
you have a flag behind you Well because well
тебя сзади флаг Ну по потому что ну
Russian people We also live and walk here
русские люди У нас тут тоже живут ходят
We have a court Russian mess she
У нас есть суд же русская мешина она
goes to school like we teach they
ходит в школу типа мы преподаёт нам
brought us textbooks Everything is in Ukrainian now
завезли учебники Всё по-украински теперь
yes but we
да но русский язык мы
teach Russian Well and in general how is this how are
преподаёт Ну а вообще как это как на это
you pulling for Selensky yes No what has this to do with it
ты за селенского тянешь да Нет причём
look okay look again it means I'm from
смотри ладно смотри ещё раз значит я из
Kursk  Here is my number from my car
Курской Вот мой от моего автомобиля
I am from Kursk region from the city of
номер Я из Курской области из города
Sudzha We have August 6 Yes the
Суджа У нас 6 августа Да пришла
Ukrainian army came here the Russian army ran
украинская армия сюда русская армия
away the Russians ran away the administration ran
убежала русские убежали администрация
away they made us an administration Yes
убежала нам сделали администрацию Да у
we have a school so that the children go to school
нас в школу чтобы дети ходили в школу
who did not leave because some left in the
кто не выехал потому что часть выехала в
course some stayed here in place Yes the
курс часть осталась тут на месте Да вот
children are studying Yes They told us Look you
детки учатся Да Нам сказали Смотри ты
can go to Kursk Yes you can
можешь выехать в Курск Да на
stay in the occupied territory to
оккупированную территорию може оста на
work in Sudzha We will simply provide a
осво в Судже работать Мы обеспечим
salary in
зарплату в
Ukraine
Украине
Ukraine region Ukraine
Украина область укра
Poma because now
Пома потому сечас
Iko Voronezh
Ико Воронеж
look at him I am 18 years old when I hit I
посмотри я его 18 лет как мне стукну я
bought myself this car full number plate
купил полною номер номе
mixed
сме сли
Ukrainian flag yes we are forbidden to drive
украинский флаг да нам Запрещают ездить
with the Russian flag already yes because well
с русским флагом уже да потому что ну
then the military
останавливает тогда военная
police stops new numbers should be sent from Sumy
полиция новые номера должны из Сум
soon car what kind of
прислать скоро машина
car What kind of Mitsubish 98 and you
ка машина Какая Mitsubish 98 года а ты
checked it out yes it seems I mean
же пробил да походу В смысле
checked it out And there is a photo Show me the car you have which one have
пробил А фото есть Покажи машину
you seen a teacher somewhere at
какой ты где-то видел преподавателя в
school in  red tie
школе в красном галстуке
you Well look everything is simple for me I could
ты Ну смотри у меня всё просто я мог
leave I could leave Yes but the kids would have been
выехать я мог выехать Да но детки бы
left without a
остались без
teacher good evening
учителя добрый вече
Artyom
Артём
name is just hard to wrap my head around
зовут просто в голове не
just a flag is hanging Yes in the Kursk region we
просто флаг висит Да в Курской области
know that there well suffered Yes Peaceful
знаем что там ну пострадал Да Мирный
people Peaceful people I will say Look at us
народ Мирный народ я скажу Смотри нас
Ukrainians not Ukrainians came no one
украинцы не украинцы пришли нас никто
at all no one touched us Yes
вообще никто не тронул Да официальные
our official authorities FSB ran away first first Armed
власти наши ФСБ убежала в первый первый
Forces FSB SU ran away when
ВС ФСБ су убежало когда ещ только
Ukrainians were just crossing the border Yes they ran
границу переходили украинцы
away even first FSB Yes there was no one
Да убежали ещё первее ФСБ Да никого не
left Yes here Ukraine came they
осталось Да вот Украина пришла нам
tell us look we are so and so you
говорят смотрите мы так и так вы
are under our protection we do not
находитесь под нашей защитой мы вас не
touch you if there is anyone military you go and
трогаем если кто есть военный вы идите
surrender there the boys came out surrendered yes he
сдайте там пацаны вышли сдались да
says You just ask me Who are you I
говорит Вы просто меня спрашивают Ты кто
say I am a teacher at school yes the
Я говорю Я преподаватель в школе да
principal of the school would be a teaching staff
директор школы на
new government
бы преподавательский соста новая власть
Yes he
Да он
says the Principal says I am
говорит Директор говорит я
in
в
wait the principal of the school says look
подожди директор школы говорит смотрите
I am outside of politics Yes a new government has come
Я вне политике Да пришла новая власть
our business is to teach children We do not interfere
наше дело учить детей Мы не вмешиваемся
in politics another government will come we
в политику вот придёт другая власть мы
will be our business  teach children Yes and We were
будем наше дело учить детей Да и Нам
offered you either can go to the
предложили вы либо можете поехать на
occupied territory in Kursk
оккупированную территорию в Курск да
or stay in the liberated territory in Sudzha to
либо остаться на освобождённый в Судже
teach children I decided that we had a
учить детей я решил вот у нас было
math teacher she went to
учительница математики она уехала в
Kursk She says I'm afraid I decided that
Курск Она говорит я боюсь я решил что я
as a man I should stay here because the
как мужчина должен остаться тут потому
children stayed we need to teach the
что дети раз остались нужно учить
children by the way and now for some reason the
детей кстати и сейчас почему-то
Russian air force is bombing our houses
Российская авиация бомбит наши вот дома
in Sudzha there are arrivals I saw a boarding house in
в Судже прилёты есть пансионат видел в
Sudzha like they blew up Well that's right she's got
Судже типа взорвали Ну правильно она
things
дела
stuck there how why look so schools
по там засели как зачем смотри так школы
we teach children here everything works the court is with
мы тут детей учим всё работает суд же у
us yes we were liberated Why do they
нас да нас освободили Зачем
put their units in tanks Look I'm
танки ставят свои подразделения Смотри
fine in court I'm happy I teach the children I have
мне в суд же хорошо Я доволен я деток
air defense Well so what happens there are no Russians there
ПВО Ну так и что получается русских там
no one left Yes I'm
нету не осталось Да я я
Russian there are no Russians there I'm Russian the
русский не осталось Да русских там Я
children are Russian we learn Russian
русский дети русские мы учим русский
at school I mean the army And the army
язык в школе я имею в виду армия А армия
didn't run away there was this regiment Akhmat He
не убежали там был этот полко Ахмат Он
ran away in the first
убежал в первые
days we'll take a photo for you Give me your photo I'll take
дни мы тебе фото сделаем Дай тво фото
no no no I'm not taking photos Okay
сделаю не не не не
okay come on  we won't Nor we
фотографирую Да всё ладно давай не будем
communicate normally
мы Нор нормально общаемся
Because I don't know maybe you know maybe
Потому что я не знаю может знаешь может
then like he'll come back to Russia like I don't
потом типа вернётся в Россию типа я не
want to have problems you
хочу чтобы проблемы у меня были
know
понимаешь
and the Ukrainian flag look well because
а украинский флаг смотри ну потому что
damn now the Ukrainian government has come
блин сейчас украинская власть пришла
Ukrainian flags I can't hang Russian ones you
украинские флаги я не могу русские
know I'm generally outside of politics
вешать понимаешь я я вообще вне политики
I just teach children Yes I tell them cases
Я просто учу детей Да я им падежи
nominative genitive accusative dative
именительный родительный винительный
instrumental prepositional That's what
дательный творительный предложный Вот
I teach them I carry the language of Pushkin
это я Учу их Я несу язык Пушкина
lermantova Well if you're so smart And what are you
лермантова Ну если ты ум такой А что ты
doing there Wait the children stayed I would have
там делаешь Подожди дети остались я бы
left long ago You know here's
уже выехал давно Понимаешь вот
some suspicious got it I mean
какой-то подозрительный понял В смысле
suspicious nutas to questions you know
подозрительный нуты на вопросы знаешь
literate person well because I'm a
грамотный вроде человек ну потому что я
teacher with a higher
учитель с высшим образованием
pedagogical education so And are you
педагогическим так А ты что в Россию
going to
будешь
return to Russia I don't think that Russia will
возвращаться Я не думаю что Россия
return here already We thought that
вернётся уже сюда тут уже Мы думали что
we were told on TV now 2 days 2
нам сказали по телевизору сейчас 2 дня 2
weeks they will liberate which region We waited
недели освободят кую область Мы ждали
waited for us Russia is not returning to us they
ждали нам Россия не возвращается намм
offered to get Ukrainian passports
предложили получить украинские паспорта
I have now submitted documents for obtaining
я подал сейчас документы на получение
Ukrainian
украинского
citizenship World Cup Why not well if
гражданства ЧМ Почему бы и нет ну если
if Russia doesn't need Sudzha if it doesn't
если России не нужна Суджа если она не
liberate us only throws bombs 8
освобождает нас только бомбы кидает 8
months Sudzha was bombed already by Russians And
месяцев бомбили суджу уже российские А
where are you now Sudzha yes
ты где сейчас находишься суджи да
Sudzha and around Show what's around you
суджи а вокруг Покажи что вокруг тебя
Why is it just interesting how I'll connect
Зачем он посто интересно как я подключу
Computer are you at school No no not at school I'm at
Компьютер ты в школе Нет не не в школе я
home
дома у себя
now nephew liberated you you're there
сейчас племянник освободил вас ты там
babbling
базаришь
somewhere in Ukraine
где-то в Украине
calm down look Sudzha Sudzha is still
успокой смотри Суджа Суджа до сих пор
under Ukraine We'll come if if
под Украиной У нас вот придёт если если
Look I wouldn't mind if yes we had
Смотри я не против если бы да у нас была
power if What flag is hanging the court is
власть если Какой флаг висит суд же
Ukrainian they came in good friend let's
украинский заходили хорошо друг давай
chat everything did
побазарим всё
there And what did you wear
дили туда А какого ты одел
there Calm down What is your
туда Успокойся Как тебя
name upo this
зовут упо это
stream
стриме
fold rest Let's
складывать покойся Давай нормально
talk normally what is your name What
поговорим как тебя зовут А тебе какая
difference does it make to you with a normal guy goril I'm not a
разница с нормальным пацаном горил я не
Streamer I'm a teacher of Russian language
Стример Я преподаватель русского языка
Lira Well tell me your last name patronymic last
Лира Ну скажи своя фамилия отчество
name patronymic and first name popk Andrey
фамилию отчество и имя попк Андрей
Vasilyevich look teacher of
Васильевич посмотри преподаватель
Russian language and literature  secondary
русского языка и литературы средне
school number 3 of the city of tsud
образовательной школы номер 3 города цуд
Okay,
Хорошо
okay, such and such, very calm, understood,
хорошо такой-то сильно спокойный понял
yes, this and also the flag Yes, this is well because
да это и ещё флаг Да это ну потому что у
we have Ukrainian flags now, I cant hang them up
нас сейчас флаги Украины я не могу
Because if they come to
вешать Потому что если придут с
check Yes, I have a Russian flag hanging, theyll
проверкой Да у меня флаг России висит
think that Im a collaborator Yes, you cant
подумают что я коллаборант Да ты не
hear and what are you afraid of, they entered your land, I
слышишь и что ты боишься на твою землю
mean Well, wait, stop, Sudzha
зашли в смысле Ну подожди стоп Суджа -
is the original Land of Kievan Rus, they
это исконно Земля Киевской Руси нам
sent us new textbooks, they
пришли нам новые учебники
gave us ru Khrushchev illegally transferred the Kursk
дали ру Хрущёв незаконно передал курскую
region to the Russian Federation Come on, lets talk
область Российской Федерации Давай давай
about history Now Im telling you Kievan
за историю Сейчас я тебе жу Киевская
Rus, ruv
Русь пори рув
transferred the Kursk region to the Russian
передал курскую область Российской
Federation, the Ukrainians came and said,
Федерации украинцы пришли говорят
look, were not occupiers, were returning, were
смотрите мы не оккупанты мы возвращаем
returning the lands of Kievan Rus and thats it Well,
возвращаем земли Киевской Руси и всё Ну
I looked Yes, everything seems correct,
я посмотрел Да вроде всё правильно
Ukraine appeared When did
появилась что Украина Когда появилась в
Ukraine appear in 1991? In 1991, it
9 году Украина В девяносто первом году
appeared And who? Who created Ukraine, sodan
появилась А да кто А кто Украину содан
died, so look, so look Lenin created
умер так смотри так смотри Ленин создал
Ukraine Yes, together with the Kursk region, and
Украину Да вместе с Курской областью а
then Khrushchev took and transferred it to the
потом Хрущёв взял и передал её
Russian
Российской
Federation, you wait  ok look the point is not
Федерации вы подожди хоро смотри суть не
that I don't look I don't argue about
в том я я не смотри я не спорю про
history I'm not a history teacher I'm a teacher of
историю Я не учитель истории Я учитель
Russian language and literature my job is to teach children and you should know again look came What flag is it now suji if it returned to suji yes Our police amini I would lead Naru Why look our charming number again who deserved the role of a teacher of Russian language and literature in the city of su
русского языка и литературы в городе су
yk piska comment whole divine throw off the banner
йк писка комент цело божественно скиньте
Hi
знам Хай
spoil the letter on y Telegram right now axis
порть пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
VN
ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the SRG ORV in your ban and very
нас через срг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show people at times I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показую информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational connections to drink
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок пить
right now and Popik there in telegram
прямо зараз а Попик там в телеграми
okrim video also other interesting and useful
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry with you  trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiynyy operative zvyazok
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chy will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe a
подпишись а